appointed by the NT for the NT convened
meeting of the equ shareholders of the
company I am attending this meeting from
icsa Lombard office in
Mumbai individual directors to introduce
themselves herself bav Das Gupta hello
I'm parab Das Gupta attending this
meeting from the corporate office at
IC Ashwin
Parn parik independent director of the
company attending this meeting from my
res in Mumbai thank
you good afternoon I UD CH independent
director of the company attending this
meeting from my residence in Mumbai
thank
you I'm surh Kumar independent director
attending this meeting from my
pres thank
youash good afternoon I V prash chat
independent director attending this
meeting from my residence in Mumbai
thank you only
Shan good afternoon I'm M shivaraman
independent director of the company
attending this meeting from a residence
in Mumbai thank
you hi I'm vishaka mul I'm attending my
meeting for my residence in
Mumbai s
Patra this is s batra attending this
meeting from my office at ICA Bank in
Mumbai
alumar bombard office in Mumbai thank
thank you sanjie MRI good afternoon I'm
sanjie MRI executive director attending
this meeting from IC Lombard office in
Mumbai apart from the board of directors
we also have Mr vikas mea company
Secretary of the company join this
meeting from ICA lomard office in Mumbai
and other key management Personnel join
this meeting Mr SN chatur partner chatur
and Company Mr R suan Narayan partner
pkf SAR and Sanam LLP the joint St
Auditors of the company have joined this
meeting Mr BB Daka designated partner
Dak and Associates LLP secretarial
auditor of the company has joined the
meeting Mr PN paric of M paric and
Associates practicing company
secretaries scrutinizers appointed by
The Honorable NT to scrutinize votes
cast electronically through remote EV
voting prior to the meeting and E voting
during the meeting has also joined this
meeting from his respective location
I sincerely thank all the equity
shareholders of the company who have
joined this meeting through VC stroke o
o the company has made necessary
arrangements to ensure participation of
equity shareholders at the meeting
through VCA mode and to enable them to
vote on the resolution set forth in the
meet notice electronically trust all of
you have referred the general
instructions for E voting and
participation in the meeting in case
Equity sholders face any difficulty they
may reach out on the helpline numbers
given on page number 11 of the notice of
the meeting under the head instructions
for Equity shareholders for attending
the meeting through VC o
VM since the meeting is held through VC
oav mode facility for appointment of
proxies was not applicable hence the
company has not provided proxy forms to
its members and did not maintain proxy
register notice convening the meeting
notice convening the meeting along with
the explanatory statement scheme and
corresponding annexures mentioned
therein was sent to the equity
shareholders of the company through
electronic mode whose email addresses
were registered with the deposit
depository participants on Wednesday
January 20 2021 a notice of a copy of
the notice scheme explanatory statement
along with the corresponding annexures
mentioned therein are available on the
website of the company at www IA
lomb.com
the website of BC limited and National
Stock Exchange of India limited
respectively and also on the website of
the National Security depository limited
the equity shareholders are now request
to note that all the documents referred
on page number 29 of the notice
convening the meeting were made
available for inspection of the equity
shareholders at the registered Office of
the company and through electronic mode
on a request in terms of the notice
convening the meeting the propos
proposal for approval of the scheme of
arrangement amongst bharati AA General
Insurance Company Limited and is Loma
General Insurance Company Limited and
their respective shareholders and
creditors under Section 230 to 232 and
other applicable provisions of the
companies act 20113 section 35 to 37 of
the insurance act 1938 is to be
considered at the meeting with the
permission of the equity shareholders I
now take the notice convening this
meeting as r The Proposal along with the
background and rational of the scheme
has been explained in the notice along
with the explanatory statement and the
annexures mentioned in the notice
convening this meeting nevertheless I
would like to mention again about the
proposal which is a Demmer of the barti
AXA non-life Insurance business into
icsa Lombard through a scheme of
arrangement bharti AXA is a limited
public limited company registered as a
general insurance company with the irdi
and is currently engaged in providing
non-life Insurance products to his
customers the proposed transaction is
expected to result in value creation for
the equity shareholders and other
stakeholders of the company through
meaningful Revenue economies of scale
growth and operational synergies policy
holders are also expected to gain from
an enhanced product suite and deeper
customer connect touch points employees
of the combined businesses will also
benefit by greater opportunities across
functions and
geographies upon this scheme becoming
effective as a consideration for the Dem
merger the company will issue an a lot
3575 6194 Equity shares of the company
of rupees 10 each fully paid up to the
equity shareholders of bti AXA based on
the valuation report submitted by the
values The Joint statutory Auditors of
the company have issued certificate
stating that the accounting treatment
specified in the scheme is in compliance
with the accounting standards prescribed
under Section 133 of the company's act
2013 the auditor certificates are also
available for inspection on the website
of the company at
www lbar.com I would like to inform to
the equity shareholder Pur to the
provisions of the companies act 2013
read with relevant rules and directions
contained in the order of the honorable
TR
the company had provided an opportunity
to its shareholders to exercise their
voting rights through electronic voting
remote e voting in respect of the
business set out in the notice convening
the meeting during the period from
Saturday February 20th 2021 starting at
9:00 a.m. IST to Monday February 22nd
2021 at 5:00 p.m. IST the company has
extended the facility of voting during
the meeting and the equity shareholders
who have not cast their vote earlier and
part participating in the meeting can
cast their votes through EV voting
module made available by national
Securities depository limited nsdl
during the
meeting the procedure for voting during
the meeting is same as the procedure for
remote EV voting provided in the notice
convening this meeting with your consent
the resolution mentioned in the notice
is taken as red and will be put to vote
shortly by electronic means only the
resolution is required to be passed with
requisite majority under Section 232 232
of the company's act
203 and applicable rules the scrutinizer
appointed by The Honorable NT namely Mr
PN parik will scrutinize votes cast
electronically through remote e voting
and E voting during the meeting and to
submit the Consolidated report of voting
to the company before vot putting the
resolution to vote I would like to
invite speaker Equity shareholders who
have the prior registration to speak
only those Equity shareholders are who
are holding Equity shares of the company
as on cut off date for E voting that is
Tuesday February 16 2021 are entitled to
participate and speak at the meeting
subject to Prior registration with due
respect to other speakers and time I
kindly request each speaker to be brief
and restrict their suggestions or
comments to 3 minutes on matter as said
for in the notice
to avoid repetition the answers to all
the questions will be provided at the
end of the Q&A session I now request the
moderator to please go ahead with the
session Mr Santosh Kumar
saraf we have received first
registration from Mr Santos Kumar
Mr Santosh Kumar saraf has not joined
this meeting uh we request our next
speaker
shareholder miss Lea
sha hello good afternoon ma'am welcome
uh can you hear me ma'am yes ma'am we
can hear you we request you to please
turn your camera on and then proceed
with your speech thank you ma'am uh
respected chairperson ma'am board of
directors and my fellow members good
afternoon to all of you myself leam
Mumbai from anderi first of all I am
very much thankful to our company
secretary Mr vikasi and his team
especially aai AR forening very good
investors services and also sending me
the NT notice by email Val time in such
a difficult situation which is full of
knowledge s and Pi in place so I am very
grateful to our compuny secretary Mr
vikasi ma'am I pray to God that he
always sh his blessing upon you I am
proud to be a shareholder of this
company ma'am I would like to ask only
two
questions my first question is how we
are encouraging our
employees my second question is what is
the road map for the next two years so I
would like to say I strongly support the
special resolutions for today's meeting
and my best wishes always our company
and this Prosperity thank you
ma'am thank you ma'am
we request our next speaker shareholder
Mr yusu
rangala to please
join Mr Yu rangala
Mr Yu rangala is not able to connect
with us can you hear my voice yes good
good good afternoon sir can you hear my
voice yes sir we can hear you sir what
only two minute my network was gone that
is why sir I'm very thankful to our
vikas sir who is a very grateful and
very very calm person and Department
will be largest in the insurance
business sir it will be largest
people infected and what are the total
people St working
after
happy thank you
sir mahra
M and please take in please take care of
all the staff and all the all the
shareholders and all people thank you
very much sir J
hind thank you Mr y
rangala we request our next speaker
shareholder Miss prakash ini
Shino good afternoon ma'am and welcome
we request you to please turn your
camera on and then kindly spe uh proceed
with your speech can you hear me Madam
yes ma'am we can hear you I'm prash sho
from Bombay respected honorable chairman
other dignitaries on the board and my
fellow shareholders good afternoon to
all of you I received the soft copy of
the egm report which is self-explanatory
I thank the company secretary Mr vkas
mea and Akay par for the same I should
not forget to once again uh thank Mr a
parik for honing me yesterday and even
today even just now and has given me the
link without which I wouldn't have been
able to speak I'm once again very very
grateful to you Mr vikas and m a g this
this the first time that a company is
conducting video conferencing meeting
due to
covid-19 we are living in a days where
everything is unpredictable lives
including our existence in such a
circumstan as running a company like ICI
lard is not a small thing I appreciate
sir sir I have few
questions what is the effect of covid-19
on our company and what are its
challenges the next question
is what is the benefit to all the
shareholders after the acquisition of
bti
EXA last but not the least we are
meeting for the first time during 20 we
are meeting over uh video conferencing
for the first time I wish one and all
good luck and happy prosperous and
healthy and Wealthy New Year I wish the
company good luck for a bright future
and pray God that the profit of the
company shall reach the peak and du Cod
sir I support the resolution put for in
today's meeting thank you
sir thank you ma'am for joining the
meeting
we now request our next and last speaker
shareholder Mr DH
baa
hello hello welcome
sir yes sir we can hear you kindly
proceed with your speech
sir
cherson director team
[Music]
insurance number
point
inv
sh
[Music]
EXP
thank you
sir we have given an opportunity to all
our speaker shareholders who had
registered with us now we request our
chairperson Madam to continue with the
speech please thank
you okay now I request Mr bav Das Gupta
managing director and CEO to respond to
the queries raised by the shareholders
thank
you uh thank you ma'am U thank you uh
respected shareholders
uh let me answer each of the questions
raised by all the uh all the
shareholders so uh Madam Lea sha first
thank you for your support and your kind
words uh you had two questions what are
we planning regarding the employees uh
so bti um General has uh at the DAT of
the transaction that we announced has
about 2,400 employees as you know ICA
group uh you know has always respected
talent and the approach that we have is
that we will look at uh Synergy and
integration of the teams uh we will
obviously want to look at giving you
know carer options to some of their uh
you know employees particularly The
Talented employees will find uh you know
lot of opportunity within IC lombar in
the merged entity the second question
that you had is the road map for the
next two years so the the the whole deal
rational is the fact that two companies
are coming together there will be lot of
synergies both on the revenue side as
also on the cost side
uh and we need to as a management team
jointly work together to you know make
that uh Synergy come through so the
focus will be in terms of execution
integrating the two organization
integrating the teams uh there is a lot
of uh you know independent Distributors
of this of the you know BAGI that we
will get so we have to integrate them in
the in the IC Lombard family so our road
map will be largely focused on uh
integrating the two teams and getting
the benefit of the Synergy that we
believe is there in this
transaction uh the second question came
from Mr yosu rangala again Mr rangala
thank you for your support uh and thank
you for the kind words uh you had two
questions one was uh about the bonus
which uh you know honestly I believe
that's a question relevant for the
larger AGM and we'll be happy to take
that question in the AGM today our
agenda is very focused on the NT mandate
uh you also had another question on
covid given that it's very topical and
there is impact for for everyone at this
point in time let me answer that
question at least for icsa Lombard uh
from the start to now we've had about
280 people who've got affected uh by the
grace of God we've not had a single uh
you know loss of life in IA Lombard and
that's largely because of the focus on
employee safety that we had right from
the beginning uh the third question came
from M prashi Sho again thank you ma'am
for your best wishes and your support uh
you had also a question of covid-19 I
think have answered that question and
the challenges that are posed by
covid-19 U you know obviously for all
businesses initially it was a very
difficult phase where we had to adjust
to uh working in this new reality um you
know Health uh claims and costs were
increasing but uh on balance as a
company we've been able to handle the
challenge and as you can see from our
numbers for 9 months uh I think we are
we are behind uh you know we've crossed
that hump we will have to watch what
happens in the next 3 months but uh
overall we remain reasonably confident
about our ability to handle the
challenge you had a question on benefit
to shareholders so if you look at the
whole deal rational U as I said there
are synergies both on the revenue side
as also in terms of the uh cost side uh
bti general you know if you look at in
terms of the size of the company uh the
size of the company is roughly about
um as on 31st March 20 2020 uh it was a
3,157 CR uh so if you look at the price
that we've paid uh the price in terms of
discount to icsa Lombard uh it is
roughly about 29% discount to our Price
to Book and uh roughly about 65%
discount to price to gwp uh so in terms
of the value to our shareholders we
believe once the Synergy and the
integration is done and the Synergy
benefit comes through we will you know
provide tremendous benefit to our
shareholders the company also comes with
lot of new Distributors particularly in
the retail side uh it has uh you know a
lot of investment that they've been
making in terms of scaling up the
business the last three four years we
believe we will be able to uh benefit
from that uh you know when we combine
the two
organizations uh the fourth question you
know speaker was Mr D baa again Mr baa
thank you for your support uh you had
three question four questions
first was in terms of position in the
marketplace and who is the number one as
of 31st March you know 2020 we were
number five and when we did the
transaction the merged entity would
become number three on a Prof fora basis
as we speak even otherwise as a company
we've moved into number three even
without the transaction being done but
this will solidify our position as
number three in the industry the number
one company is New
India uh you asked a question on the
investment that we will get the
investment book of bti AI is about
4,800 that will come to us as part of
the uh
transaction uh you also asked a question
of number of shares and the dilution uh
so the dilution is about 7.3% and the
number of shares is
uh uh about 35 million shares uh so post
the integration we will have we will
issue
35.75 million shares and the effective
dilution will be about 7.3% of the
company you had another question in
terms of the business of baji bgi is in
the same business as US general
insurance they write motor Health uh
crop corporate lines all you know all
segments of business that you know that
we are also presented but there is uh
you know within the large opportunity
there are certain uh specifics of market
segments that they are strong in and
that's where we believe there will be a
lot of synergy between the two of us I
think that was your last question thank
you
the queries have now been answered as
mentioned earlier those who have not
cast their vote on the resolution set
for in the notice may do so now as the
EV voting platform is available for the
next 30 minutes I declare the meeting as
closed as soon as the voting on The
Resolution has been completed by the
equity shareholders through e voting I
authorize the whole time director of the
company or the company secretary to
declare the results of the e- remote e
voting as well as for the electronic
voting done at the meeting today along
with the scrutinizers report the results
will be announced within 48 hours from
the conclusion of the meeting that is on
or before Thursday February 25th 2021 to
the stock exchanges where the equity
shares of the company are listed and
shall also be displayed at the notice
board of the registered Office of the
company and hosted on the website of the
company and on the website of n s DL
along with the scrutinizers report the
same would also be duly recorded as part
of the proceedings of the meeting this
concludes the formal business of the
meeting before I conclude on behalf of
the company I wish to place on record
our gratitude to all our shareholders
creditors Distributors and Regulatory
author authorities for their cooperation
and active participation in the
proceedings and for their valuable
suggestions and all the employees for
their hard work and their commitment
please stay healthy and stay safe and
take care of yourselves thank you very
much have a good day namas
[Music]
that's
all are we meeting again for a digital
presentation I think they will send a
separate link for
that okay okay so we can log out we not
wait till 4:30 I mean if everybody's
okay we can
continue yeah we can check with them
actually that's a good idea we can have
that presentation
earlier I think the otherwise they have
given time of 4:30 I set up at 4:30